RG 062:063, Town of Hampton
Connecticut State Library
Town of Hampton records
1748-1929
Connecticut State Library
Hampton (Conn.)
5 cubic feet
Tax and school records for the town of Hampton.
RG062_063
T000345
Historical Note
The town of Hampton was incorporated in October 1786 and was taken from Windham, Pomfret, Brooklyn, Canterbury, Mansfield.
Scope and Content
Tax and school records for the town of Hampton.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Hampton; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Hampton; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Hampton; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Hampton
Places:
Hampton (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1748-1929
  - Rate bills, Second Society, 1772-1803 (Box Box 1)
    fragments
  - David Strong's receipt for keeping school, 1748 (Box Box 1)
  - Tax Abstracts
    Tax abstracts for 1914 to 1929 are not boxed.
    - 1852, 1853, 1854, 1855-1856, 1857, 1858-1859, 1860-1861-1862, 1863-1864, 1865-1866, 1867-1868, 1869 (Box Box 2)
    - 1870-1871, 1872-1873, 1874-1875, 1876, 1877-1878, 1879-1880, 1881, 1882-1883 (Box Box 3)
    - 1886-1887, 188-1889, 1890-1891, 1892-1893-1894, 1895, 1896-1897, 1898 (Box Box 4)
    - 1899-1900, 1901-1902-1903, 1904-1905-1906, 1907-1908-1909, 1910, 1911-1912-1913 (Box Box 5)
    - 1914, 1 volume
    - 1915, 1 volume
    - 1916, 1 volume
    - 1917, 1 volume
    - 1918, 1 volume
    - 1919, 1 volume
    - 1920, 1 volume
    - 1921, 1 volume
    - 1922, 1 volume
    - 1923, 1 volume
    - 1924, 1 volume
    - 1925, 1 volume
    - 1926, 1 volume
    - 1927, 1 volume
    - 1928, 1 volume
    - 1929, 1 volume